# **Pranjal Pandey**

Kathmandu 9819173663 pranjalpandey92@gmail.com

An enthusiastic Computer Science student currently in the final year of Bachelor's Degree with one year of working experience as a Python web developer in Logispark Technology. Inclined towards computer programming and constantly likes to learn new technologies. Currently, working as a freelancer in a small startup tech company. Passionate about Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence and have a keen interest in Astronomy.

## **Work Experience**

### Freelancer

12/2019 to Present

Eklavya Technology

Kathmandu

- Completed an E-commerce project for a Handicraft Company. Implemented user authorization, authentication, roles assignment, order products, etc and designed an admin dashboard to track the order history.
- Completed a Construction Mart Market place for a Hardware Company where user can create their account and sell their own products upon getting access from the admin. Handled user authorization, authentication, roles assignment, order products as well as designed an individual dashboard page for the registered user.
- Successfully designed and hosted a static website for a microfinance company.

### **Teacher / Instructor**

11/2019 to 12/2019

Shree Shivapur Higher Secondary School

Rupandehi, Nepal

Taught Computer Science and Mathematics to the students of grade 6 to 9 during the Teaching Fellowship program organized by Deerwalk Institute of Technology in the winter of 2019

# Python Django Developer (Intern)

07/2018 to 07/2019

Logispark Technology

Teku, Kathmandu

- · Worked productively with the team to understand requirements and business specification.
- Effectively coded software changes and alternations based on specific design.
- Worked to solve challenging real world problems using the latest web technologies.
- Researching, designing, implementing and managing software programs.
- Identifying areas for modification in existing programs and subsequently developing these modifications.
- Successfully completed 3 major commercial projects during the tenure.

# Skills Python Django HTML / CSS Git / GitHub PHP / Laravel SQL REST API JavaScript Teaching Teamwork

### **Education**

# **Deerwalk Institute of Technology**

Bachelor's Computer Science Sifal, Kathmandu 11/2016 to Present

# **Uniglobe College HSS**

High school or equivalent Computer Science and Mathematics Kamaladi, Kathmandu 07/2014 to 08/2016

### **Awards**

# Silver Medal, Chemistry Theory Papers, International Science Olympiad

2016

• Won silver medal in International Science Olympiad on Chemistry theory papers, held in India, New Delhi, 2016.

### **Mathematics Quiz Contest**

2014

· Winner of inter-school mathematics guiz competition held at Annapurna Higher Secondary School.

### **Deerwalk Scholarship**

2018

• Granted scholarships for multiple times by the Deerwalk Administration due to outstanding achievements in the academics and project works

### **Groups**

# **Deerwalk Literature Society**

Contributed as an active member and a vice president at the Deerwalk Literature Society where the club members and guests held multiple book reading sessions and engaged in serious discussions about different topics on or off the books.

### **Uniglobe Research Center**

One of the founders of the Uniglobe Research Center which acted as a place to demonstrate one s knowledge in building fun science projects.

### Links

Website: https://pranjal07pandey.github.io/portfolio/

GitHub: https://github.com/pranjal07pandey

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pranjal-pandey-41593715b/